staxus.com 2017-11-20

# Staxus.com - Tour Area

Staxus.com places a high value on the privacy on all our customers, and as such we have a process to protect and respect the privacy of our visitors as well as our registered users. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any new policy here. By using or navigating around the site, or by using any of the services that we provide here, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be fully bound by this Privacy Statement. If for any reason you do not agree to be so bound, do not remain on the site. 

**Contact Information:** Your contact information (e.g. your name and e-mail address) may be used to communicate with you when necessary with respect to transactions conducted through the site and material changes in the site's policies (we may also send you information about Staxus.com). We agree not to sell, share or rent any contact information collected from you except as hereby disclosed in this statement. All payment information provided to the site is maintained on our secure servers. 

**Financial Information:** Your financial information (e.g. your credit card information) is collected on an as-needed basis in order that we may bill you for services that you have purchased through the site. We agree not to sell, share or rent any financial information from you except as necessary to fulfill our services. All financial information provided to the site is maintained on secure servers of Humboldt and we have no access to this information. 

**Data Protection:** According to European and International data protection laws, the personal information collected on this website will be used by Staxus.com to provide you with the service requested and inform you about promotional activities. You may ask us for details of the personal information relating to you that we hold, and you may also ask us to rectify, cancel or refuse the personal data processing by contacting Staxus.com. It is always our policy to preserve user privacy, but we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.
